hey guys me and geordie just wanted you to know that we're proud of you right geordies
yes because you're getting it listen i know that it's taken a while all right you don't have to do
the whole yawn thing we're not trying to shade them we're trying to congratulate because even
though not everybody's getting it more are getting it than ever we see you we see we do
you don't well i do i see you reading between the lines i see you doing the math i see you realizing
that a conspiracy theory is really just figuring out the surreptitious planning that has gone into
an event that you are being told is something other than what it is i see it it's beautiful it's
beautiful you're beautiful
you're beautiful
you